const data = {
  CssIQData: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: `1) What is CSS?`,
      answer: `Css stands for cascading style sheet.--It's a style sheet language that determines how the elements contents in the page are looke shown.--Css is used to develop a beautiful page with colors, spacing, sizes and others styles.`,
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: `2) Which company developed CSS?`,
      answer: `Was created by World Wide Web Consortium W3C.--It was first released on December 17, 1996`,
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: `3) What is the Box Model in css?`,
      answer: `The css Box Model is essentially a box that wraps around every HTML element.--It consists in: --1) Margins.--2) Borders. --3) Padding.--4) Content.`,
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: `4) How to include css in the webpage?`,
      answer: `There are different ways to include css in the webpage, for example:--1) External style sheet.--2) Embed css with a style tag.--3) Add inline style to HTML elements.--4) Import a stylesheet file.`,
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: `5) How to make rounded corner using CSS ?`,
      answer: `To create a rounded corner, we use the CSS border-radius property. --This property is used to set the border radius of the element.`,
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: `6) What is Flexbox in CSS?`,
      answer: `Flexbox, or the Flexible Box Layout, is a CSS3 layout mode that offers an efficient way to distribute space and align items in a container, even when their size is unknown or dynamic. It's especially useful for responsive design.`,
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: `7) What are CSS Selectors?`,
      answer: `CSS selectors are patterns used to select elements to style. Types of selectors include class, id, attribute, and pseudo-class selectors, each allowing for different styling approaches.`,
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: `8) What is CSS Grid Layout?`,
      answer: `CSS Grid Layout is a two-dimensional layout system for the web. It lets you layout items into rows and columns, and it's one of the most powerful layout systems available in CSS.`,
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: `9) How can you create a responsive design with CSS?`,
      answer: `Responsive design in CSS can be achieved using flexible grids, flexible images, and media queries, allowing web pages to adapt to the screen size of different devices.`,
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: `10) What are Media Queries in CSS?`,
      answer: `Media queries are a CSS technique used to apply styles based on the media type, screen dimensions, and other device features. They are a cornerstone of responsive web design.`,
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: `11) What is the difference between padding and margin in CSS?`,
      answer: `Padding is the space inside the border of an element, while margin is the space outside the border. Padding affects the element's size, while margin affects the spacing between elements.`,
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: `12) How do you use variables in CSS?`,
      answer: `CSS variables, also known as custom properties, are entities defined by CSS authors that contain specific values to be reused throughout a document. They are set using the -- notation.`,
    },
    {
      id: 13,
      question: `13) What is the purpose of the z-index in CSS?`,
      answer: `The z-index property in CSS controls the vertical stacking order of elements that overlap. Elements with a higher z-index cover those with a lower one.`,
    },
    {
      id: 14,
      question: `14) What are Pseudo-classes in CSS?`,
      answer: `Pseudo-classes are used to define special states of an element. For example, :hover applies a style when the user hovers over an element, and :first-child targets the first element in a group.`,
    },
    {
      id: 15,
      question: `15) How do you implement a web font in a CSS file?`,
      answer: `Web fonts can be implemented using the @font-face rule, which allows you to download a font from the internet and display it on your web page.`,
    },
    {
      id: 16,
      question: `16) What is the difference between inline and block elements in CSS?`,
      answer: `Inline elements do not start on a new line and only occupy the space bounded by the tags, while block elements start on a new line and occupy the full width available.`,
    },
    {
      id: 17,
      question: `17) What is a CSS Preprocessor?`,
      answer: `A CSS preprocessor is a scripting language that extends CSS and then compiles it into regular CSS. Examples include Sass, LESS, and Stylus. They add functionalities like variables, nesting, and mixins.`,
    },
    {
      id: 18,
      question: `18) What is the CSS 'display' property used for?`,
      answer: `The display property in CSS is used to determine how an element is displayed on the webpage. Common values include block, inline, inline-block, none, and grid.`,
    },
    {
      id: 19,
      question: `19) How do you make a website's layout mobile-friendly?`,
      answer: `To make a layout mobile-friendly, use responsive design practices like fluid grids, responsive images, and CSS media queries to ensure your site looks good on all devices.`,
    },
    {
      id: 20,
      question: `20) What are CSS Animations?`,
      answer: `CSS animations are a way to animate transitions from one CSS style configuration to another. They provide a way to control animation speed, direction, timing, and repetition.`,
    },
    {
      id: 21,
      question: `21) How do you handle browser-specific styling?`,
      answer: `Browser-specific styling can be managed using vendor prefixes in CSS, ensuring compatibility across different browsers and handling specific browser quirks.`,
    },
    {
      id: 22,
      question: `22) What are SVGs in CSS?`,
      answer: `SVGs, or Scalable Vector Graphics, are an XML-based image format for two-dimensional graphics. They can be styled and animated with CSS and are ideal for high-quality graphics on the web.`,
    },
    {
      id: 23,
      question: `23) How can CSS be used to create a grid layout?`,
      answer: `CSS can create a grid layout using the CSS Grid Layout system, which allows for the creation of complex, responsive web layouts with rows and columns.`,
    },
    {
      id: 24,
      question: `24) What is the purpose of CSS Frameworks?`,
      answer: `CSS Frameworks provide a basic structure for designing web pages and applications, offering pre-written CSS files with standard settings to simplify the design process. Examples include Bootstrap and Tailwind CSS.`,
    },
    {
      id: 25,
      question: `25) What is the Cascade in CSS?`,
      answer: `The Cascade is a fundamental concept in CSS that determines how to combine property values originating from different sources. It essentially decides how to resolve conflicts when multiple rules apply to the same element.`,
    },
    {
      id: 26,
      question: `26) How do you optimize CSS for performance?`,
      answer: `Optimizing CSS for performance involves minimizing file sizes, reducing the use of complex selectors, leveraging CSS shorthand properties, and eliminating unused CSS.`,
    },
    {
      id: 27,
      question: `27) What are CSS Transitions?`,
      answer: `CSS Transitions are a way to create smooth animations when changing from one CSS style to another. They allow control over the duration and timing of the transition effects.`,
    },
    {
      id: 28,
      question: `28) How do you make text responsive in CSS?`,
      answer: `Making text responsive in CSS involves using relative units like percentages, ems, or viewport units for font sizes, along with media queries for adjustments at different screen sizes.`,
    },
    {
      id: 29,
      question: `29) What are the benefits of using CSS Variables?`,
      answer: `CSS Variables offer easier maintenance, better readability, and more flexibility in your stylesheets, allowing values to be reused and changed in one place.`,
    },
    {
      id: 30,
      question: `30) What is the role of the 'position' property in CSS?`,
      answer: `The 'position' property in CSS specifies how an element is positioned in a document. It can be static, relative, absolute, fixed, or sticky, each defining how the element interacts with the flow of the document.`,
    },
    
  ],
  HtmlIQData: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: `1) What is HTML?`,
      answer: `HTML is an acronym which stands for Hyper Text Markup Language which is used for creating web pages and web applications.`,
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: `2) What is a tag?`,
      answer: `HTML tags are symbols between which content is placed.`,
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: `3) What is an attribute?`,
      answer: `HTML attributes are special words used inside the opening tag to control the element's behaviour.`,
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: `4) What is the difference between block and inline elements?`,
      answer: `Block elements are scheduled to take up as much space as they can. In contrast, inline elements have been designed to take up as little space as possible.`,
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: `5) What are semantic elements?`,
      answer: `A semantic element clearly describes its meaning to both the browser and the developer.
      --Examples of non-semantic elements: <div> and <span>: --Do not say anything about their content.
      --Examples of semantic elements: --<form>, <table> and <article> - Clearly define its content.`,
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: `6) Indicate some semantic labels?`,
      answer: `--<item>
              --<aside>
              --<details>
              --<figcaption>
              --<figure>
              --<footer>
              --<header>
              --<main>
              --<mark>
              --<navigation>
              --<section>
              --<summary>
              --<time>`,
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: `7) How to Use the Section Element in HTML?`,
      answer: `The section element should only be used if there isn't a more specific element. 
      --For example, you wouldn't use a <section> tag to create a footer, but use the <footer> tag instead. 
      --But you would use the <section> tag to break up a one page website.`,
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: `8) Do all HTML tags have an end tag?`,
      answer: `There are some HTML tags that don't need a closing tag.`,
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: `9) Are the HTML tags and elements the same thing?`,
      answer: `Are not the same thing. Because the element contain tags and content.--For example: <p>Parrafo</p>
      --And the tags are only, the start tags <p> and the end tags </p>.`,
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: `10) What is the 'class' attribute in HTML?`,
      answer: `The attribute class is placed inside the start tag and multiple tags can have the same class.`,
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: `11) What is the purpose of the 'alt' attribute in images?`,
      answer: `The 'alt' attribute provides alternative text for an image if it cannot be displayed. It's crucial for accessibility, helping screen readers describe images to visually impaired users.`,
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: `12) How do you create a hyperlink in HTML?`,
      answer: `Hyperlinks are created using the <a> tag, with the 'href' attribute specifying the link's destination. For example: <a href='url'>link text</a>.`,
    },
    {
      id: 13,
      question: `13) What is the difference between <section> and <div> tags?`,
      answer: `<section> is a semantic tag that represents a thematic grouping of content, while <div> is a non-semantic container used for styling purposes without implying any meaning.`,
    },
    {
      id: 14,
      question: `14) What is the purpose of the <head> element in an HTML document?`,
      answer: `The <head> element contains meta-information about the document, such as its title, links to scripts and stylesheets, and other meta tags.`,
    },
    {
      id: 15,
      question: `15) What are <iframe> tags used for in HTML?`,
      answer: `<iframe> tags are used to embed another HTML document within the current document, like embedding a YouTube video or a map.`,
    },
    {
      id: 16,
      question: `16) What is the purpose of the <nav> element?`,
      answer: `The <nav> element is used to define a set of navigation links. It's a semantic element that helps with SEO and accessibility.`,
    },
    {
      id: 17,
      question: `17) How do you create a list in HTML?`,
      answer: `Lists in HTML can be created using the <ul> (unordered list) and <ol> (ordered list) elements, with <li> tags for each list item.`,
    },
    {
      id: 18,
      question: `18) What is the purpose of the 'doctype' declaration?`,
      answer: `The 'doctype' declaration tells the browser which version of HTML the page is written in. It must be the first line of any HTML document.`,
    },
    {
      id: 19,
      question: `19) How can HTML5 be used for multimedia embedding?`,
      answer: `HTML5 introduces elements like <audio> and <video> for embedding sound and video directly into web pages without needing external plugins.`,
    },
    {
      id: 20,
      question: `20) What are data-* attributes used for in HTML?`,
      answer: `Data-* attributes are used to store custom data on HTML elements. They provide a way to add extra information to standard HTML elements.`,
    },
    {
      id: 21,
      question: `21) What is the purpose of the <footer> element?`,
      answer: `The <footer> element is used to define a footer for a document or section and usually contains authorship information, copyright notices, and navigation links.`,
    },
    {
      id: 22,
      question: `22) What is HTML5 Canvas?`,
      answer: `The HTML5 <canvas> element is used to draw graphics on a web page using JavaScript. It can be used for animations, game graphics, data visualizations, and photo manipulations.`,
    },
    {
      id: 23,
      question: `23) How do you make a form in HTML?`,
      answer: `Forms in HTML are made using the <form> element, which can contain input elements like text fields, checkboxes, radio buttons, and submit buttons.`,
    },
    {
      id: 24,
      question: `24) What is the difference between GET and POST methods in form submissions?`,
      answer: `In GET method, form data is appended to the action URL and visible in the browser's address bar. POST method sends data through the request body, so it's not visible in the URL.`,
    },
    {
      id: 25,
      question: `25) What is the use of the <table> element?`,
      answer: `The <table> element is used to create a table in HTML. It's accompanied by <tr> (table row), <th> (table header), and <td> (table data) elements.`,
    },
    {
      id: 26,
      question: `26) What are inline styles in HTML?`,
      answer: `Inline styles in HTML are used to apply unique styling to an element directly within its opening tag using the 'style' attribute.`,
    },
    {
      id: 27,
      question: `27) What is the role of HTML in web development?`,
      answer: `HTML forms the backbone of web pages, defining the structure and layout of content on the web. It's the standard markup language for creating web pages.`,
    },
    {
      id: 28,
      question: `28) How do you use comments in HTML?`,
      answer: `Comments in HTML are made using <!-- and --> tags. They're used to add explanatory notes in the code which aren't displayed in the browser.`,
    },
    {
      id: 29,
      question: `29) What is the difference between <strong> and <b> tags?`,
      answer: `<strong> is a semantic tag indicating important text, while <b> is a stylistic tag that bolds text without implying any added importance.`,
    },
    {
      id: 30,
      question: `30) What are HTML Entities?`,
      answer: `HTML entities are used to represent special characters in HTML. They start with an ampersand (&) and end with a semicolon (;) like &lt; for the less-than sign.`,
    },    
  ],
  JsIQData: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: `1) What is JavaScript?`,
      answer: `JavaScript is the programming language for the web, it can update and change both HTML and CSS and it can also calculate, manipulate and validate data, it is a language that works on the client and server side.`,
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: `2) What are JavaScript data types?`,
      answer: `There are two types of data: --The primitive data type can only store a single data whereas the object can store colletion of data.`,
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: `3) What is JavaScript standard?`,
      answer: `The JavaScript standard is the ECMAScript`,
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: `4) What is ECMAScript?`,
      answer: `ECMA is an acronym for the European Computer Manufacturers Association, which develops standards for information technology.--It is a general purpose programming language that is implemented in JavaScript.`,
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: `5) Which company developed JavaScript?`,
      answer: `Was created by Brendan Eich at Netscape Communications Corporation, for the Netscape navigator web browser.`,
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: `6) What are non-primitive data types in JavaScript?`,
      answer: `The non-primitive are:--Class, Object, Array.`,
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: `7) What is the use of the let keyword in JavaScript?`,
      answer: `It is used to handle a data type in a specific scope, for example, in methods. `,
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: `8) How do you initialize a variable in JavaScript?`,
      answer: `We use assignment operator = for set the value of a variable.`,
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: `9) How do you declare a variable?`,
      answer: `It is declared using the var, const, and let keywords.`,
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: `10) What is typeof operator for?`,
      answer: `Typeof operator in JavaScript is an operator used for type checking and returns the data type of the operand passed to it.`,
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: `11) What is concat?`,
      answer: `Adding, linking or interlinking content.`,
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: `12) What is “This” Keyword in Javascript?`,
      answer: `"This" keyword refers to an object that is executing the current piece.`,
    },
    {
      id: 13,
      question: `13) What are callbacks?`,
      answer: `A callback is a function that will be executed after another function gets executed.`,
    },
    {
      id: 14,
      question: `14) What is NaN property in JavaScript?`,
      answer: `NaN property represents “Not-a-Number” value.--For example:--isNaN("Hello")=>Returns true
      --isNaN(345)=>Returns false--isNaN(undefined)=>Returns true`,
    },
    {
      id: 15,
      question: `15) What is an IIFE in JavaScript?`,
      answer: `Is a function that runs as soon as it is defined.`,
    },
    {
      id: 16,
      question: `16) What is DOM?`,
      answer: `DOM stands for Document Object Model.--When the browser tries to render an HTML document, it creates an object based on the HTML document called DOM.`,
    },
    {
      id: 17,
      question: `17) What is === operator?`,
      answer: `=== is called a strict equality operator, which returns true when the two operands have the same value without conversion.`,
    },
    {
      id: 18,
      question: `18) What are all the looping structures in JavaScript?`,
      answer: `Following are looping structures in Javascript:
      --For
      --While
      --Do-while`,
    },
    {
      id: 19,
      question: `19) How can you convert the string of any base to an integer in JavaScript?`,
      answer: `The parseInt() function is used to convert numbers between different bases. parseInt() takes the string to be converted as its first parameter. --The second parameter is the base of the given string.`,
    },
    {
      id: 20,
      question: `20) What is ! operator?`,
      answer: `It is a logical NOT operator, its main function is to negate the value.`,
    },
    {
      id: 21,
      question: `21) What is the difference between the && operator and || operator?`,
      answer: `The || operator must execute one of two statements, on the other hand, the && operator must execute the two statements.`,
    },
    {
      id: 22,
      question: `22) What is a Promise in JavaScript?`,
      answer: `A Promise is an object representing the eventual completion or failure of an asynchronous operation. It's a way for handling asynchronous operations in JavaScript, allowing you to write code that assumes a value will eventually be returned.`,
    },
    {
      id: 23,
      question: `23) What are Arrow Functions?`,
      answer: `Arrow functions are a concise way to write function expressions in JavaScript. They allow shorter syntax compared to traditional function expressions and do not have their own 'this', arguments, super, or new.target.`,
    },
    {
      id: 24,
      question: `24) What is event bubbling in JavaScript?`,
      answer: `Event bubbling is a method of event propagation in the HTML DOM where events propagate from the deepest, innermost element (the event target) up through the ancestors in the hierarchy.`,
    },
    {
      id: 25,
      question: `25) What is a closure in JavaScript?`,
      answer: `A closure is a feature in JavaScript where an inner function has access to the outer (enclosing) function's variables — a scope chain. Closures are used for implementing privacy and state in objects.`,
    },
    {
      id: 26,
      question: `26) How do you create an object in JavaScript?`,
      answer: `Objects in JavaScript can be created using object literals, using the 'new' keyword, or using Object.create(). Object literals are the simplest way to create objects.`,
    },
    {
      id: 27,
      question: `27) What are JavaScript Modules?`,
      answer: `JavaScript modules are reusable pieces of code that can be exported from one program and imported for use in another program. Modules make it easier to structure and maintain large JavaScript applications.`,
    },
    {
      id: 28,
      question: `28) What is the difference between '==' and '===' in JavaScript?`,
      answer: `'==' checks for equality only, while '===' checks for both equality and type, which means '===' is a stricter comparison than '=='.`,
    },
    {
      id: 29,
      question: `29) What are JavaScript Higher Order Functions?`,
      answer: `Higher order functions are functions that operate on other functions, either by taking them as arguments or by returning them. They are a key part of functional programming in JavaScript.`,
    },
    {
      id: 30,
      question: `30) What is an event loop in JavaScript?`,
      answer: `The event loop is a process in JavaScript that continuously checks the call stack and if it's empty, it looks into the message queue. If there's a pending callback, it pushes it to the call stack to execute.`,
    },    
  ],
  LinuxCommands: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: `1) pwd`,
      answer: `The pwd command writes to standard output the full path name of your current directory.`,
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: `2) cd`,
      answer: `This command is used to navigate through the Linux files and directories, to continue we must know about the word "PATH". 
      --The path is one of the most essential concepts in Linux and this is something every Linux user should know.
      --A path is a way to refer to files and directories, it tells us where we are now or where we are going.
      --Important note:
      --The absolute path always starts at the root (/) directory. 
      --For example, /home/Documents/Programmation/Class1
      --A relative path starts from the current directory. 
      --For example, if you are in the /Documents directory and want to access the Class1 directory, you can use /Programmation/Class1`,
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: `3) ls`,
      answer: `The ls command is used to list files, it will print the contents of that current folder.--Exists many flags for each command, one of my favorites is the flag -a in the command ls. --For example: --ls -a, this command, will list all files of the current folder up to the hidden ones. `,
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: `4) mkdir`,
      answer: `With this command, you will create folders in a simple way for example: -- mkdir folder1.--Also, you can create multiple folders for example: --mkdir folder1 folder2, folder2 is not inside folder1, but next to it.`,
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: `5) rmdir`,
      answer: `If you can create folders also you can remove folders with the command rmdir, for remove one folder the simple way, type rmdir [name folder]. --For example: -- rmdir folder1,  and you're done.--Ok, another flag favorite is -rf with this command rmdir -rf, it will remove the folder with files inside it is very useful.`,
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: `6) touch`,
      answer: `Now, as I said mkdir is for creating a folder, and the command touch is for creating a file.--It is important that you know that when you create a file it will be empty.`,
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: `7) cat`,
      answer: `The cat (concatenate) command is used to display the content of files. It's commonly used to quickly view small files, combine files, or add content to the end of a file. For example, 'cat file.txt' will display the contents of 'file.txt'.`,
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: `8) grep`,
      answer: `grep is a powerful command used for pattern searching in files. It's used to search for a specific string of characters within files. For example, 'grep "text" file.txt' will search for the word "text" in 'file.txt' and display the lines where it appears.`,
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: `9) chmod`,
      answer: `chmod (change mode) is used to change the access permissions of files and directories. For example, 'chmod 755 file.txt' changes the permissions of 'file.txt' to be readable and executable by everyone, but only writable by the file owner.`,
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: `10) chown`,
      answer: `chown (change owner) is used to change the ownership of a file or directory. For example, 'chown user:group file.txt' will change the ownership of 'file.txt' to 'user' and assign it to the 'group'.`,
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: `11) df`,
      answer: `df (disk free) is used to display the amount of available disk space for file systems. For example, 'df -h' provides a human-readable format of space left on all mounted file systems.`,
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: `12) du`,
      answer: `du (disk usage) shows the space used by files and directories. It's commonly used to find out which files or directories are using up the most disk space. For example, 'du -sh *' shows the size of all files and folders in the current directory in a human-readable format.`,
    },
    {
      id: 13,
      question: `13) tail`,
      answer: `The tail command is used to display the last part of a file. It's particularly useful for viewing the newest entries in log files. For example, 'tail -n 10 file.log' displays the last 10 lines of 'file.log'.`,
    },
    {
      id: 14,
      question: `14) head`,
      answer: `Similar to tail, head displays the first part of a file. For example, 'head -n 10 file.txt' will show the first 10 lines of 'file.txt'.`,
    },
    {
      id: 15,
      question: `15) find`,
      answer: `The find command is used to search and locate the list of files and directories based on conditions you specify. For example, 'find / -name filename.txt' searches for a file named 'filename.txt' in the root directory and all its subdirectories.`,
    },
    {
      id: 16,
      question: `16) kill`,
      answer: `kill is used to terminate a process. You need to know the process ID (PID) for the command to work. For example, 'kill 1234' would terminate the process with PID 1234.`,
    },
    {
      id: 17,
      question: `17) cp`,
      answer: `cp (copy) is used to copy files and directories. For example, 'cp file1.txt file2.txt' copies the contents of 'file1.txt' to 'file2.txt'.`,
    },
    {
      id: 18,
      question: `18) mv`,
      answer: `mv (move) is used to move or rename files and directories. For example, 'mv file1.txt new_file.txt' renames 'file1.txt' to 'new_file.txt'.`,
    },
    {
      id: 19,
      question: `19) who`,
      answer: `The who command displays who is logged on the system. It provides a list of users currently logged into the computer.`,
    },
    {
      id: 20,
      question: `20) man`,
      answer: `man (manual) displays the user manual of any command that we can run on the terminal. For example, 'man ls' shows the manual pages for the 'ls' command.`,
    }    
  ],
};

// Export data
export default data;
